Yoo-hoo!
It's Shoko Ann!
Where are you today, Shoko?
On the sea!
We're here today to catch octopus!
Yay! Tako!
It's like a semi-private thing.
It's like the cameras are rolling on our private life.
Last time, Milinya, Sana, me and Maika went fishing.
We caught maggot and scorpionfish.
Shoko went private once, too.
I caught horse mackerel and sea bass in private.
This time, I caught an octopus instead of a fish, so I was happy and enjoyed it.
I'm happy and looking forward to it!
I'll do my best to catch it!
I hope this video won't be with okra!
I'll do my best!
I'm off!
Off to sea!
I'm off.
Bye-bye.
They waved to me.
Mr. Absolute, these people... they're smiling.
Bye-bye!
You're so sweet!
I've been waving to everyone I pass.
Cheerful!
Fun! It's like an attraction!
Hey!
Point! Point! It's like an attraction!
Poison Poison.
Poison has that make-up.
It wasn't there.
What colour do you like to wear?
Cute.
Does it really matter what colour?
Does it matter? It doesn't matter.
Just a colour you like?
I like this one.
My set.
The word ‘hegi’...
I think of a tiki thumping on the seabed.
That's great.
Do you think I can catch an octopus?
I'd love to.
You can't catch an octopus if you say the octopus is friendly.
You can't catch octopus even if they're nice to you.
You're never going to catch a walleye?
Can't you ever catch a walleye?
I want to rely on Dr. Google.
Dr. Google, it'd be great if we could catch one.
Let's work together.
The takoyaki will be waiting for us.
If we don't have that, what'll happen to the takoyaki, the takoyaki will be waiting for us.
Where's it going to be?
They're making takoyaki over here.
Actually...
I'll give you a ticket.
But, you know, if this is out, it might mean we're catching fish.
Or it's something else.
What is it?
I'll have it edited, I'm sure it's either that, or something else is happening, or something...
I'll get it edited, absolutely.
I'll see what happens.
It's like on either side, isn't it?
Press the button.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
It's pretty much stopped.
Let's wind it up.
And thump, thump.
Fishing pictures are difficult because you never know when you'll catch a fish.
You have to keep turning it.
Hang on, Shoko Shoko, hang on.
I didn't get it at all.
Hang in there!
Octopus, you're doing great! I had no idea the manager was here.
He said you're here.
Where do I hold it?
Range.
Yes, sir.
It's so much charcoal.
It's a lot of charcoal.
There's more than usual.
Why?
Sorry.
You don't like it?
I thought you were filming.
They're filming.
They're doing it.
You've been using it? Thank you very much.
I can really feel it.
That's nice.
The symbol's still going strong.
That's great.
Taco man.
That wasn't fast.
I had no idea.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God.
It's all black.
Take it from over here.
Really? - Yeah.
Look.
You're totally black.
It's all black.
Atachi, black.
Atachi.
Atachi, wait.
If you don't do this pink thing, the signing's in trouble.
The signing's in trouble, the signing's in trouble!
It's just an octopus.
Sorry, just an octopus.
Aww...
Oh, my God.
The back's in trouble!
It's a pattern.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
It's a pattern.
It's a pretty pattern.
But it's good.
We can make takoyaki.
Yes, you can.
If we don't catch any fish, we'll just...
If we don't catch any fish, we'll just come to the sea.
If we don't catch any fish, we'll just come to the ocean and get covered in charcoal.
Oh, no.
I'll do my best.
I'll try my best.
What's the trick? Miss Shoko.
What? I really didn't know.
I think it's important to be aware.
You never know if they might be there.
Oh, you dropped it right away.
But what?
It got stuck. It's like...
It's gone.
It just fell off.
I don't know.
Come on!
I can't! I can't lose!
That's great! You're so big! I can't lose!
I've won!
Big!
Aah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's huge! Oh, my God!
That's great.
Oh, my God!
It's so big.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to fake a smile.
Oh, my God.
I made it.
It's coming out that this is bad.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
I'm coming... maybe he's thinking about me... maybe he's thinking about me...
Maybe he's thinking of me... or maybe he's thinking of me... or maybe he's thinking of me... but we don't have enough pins.
I'm so heavy...
Suddenly I'm light.
It's so heavy!
I've caught the earth.
I've caught the Earth!
I have the strength and patience not to get seasick.
But, but...
But, but... End.
Finished. Bye-bye, Octopus.
Too bad. I'm glad I took you.
Sure, I'll come back.
How many total? Total.
Four octopuses. Four octopuses.
Four octopuses. We've been at it for two hours.
Then we're going home.
Look, gentlemen.
Octopus.
Four octopuses in two hours is a lot, I'll give you that.
Yay, you've got one.
So we're going to boil them and eat them, and then...
We're going to have an octopus party.
Let's have fun. I'm so happy. I'm going to try this.
Choco-takoyaki. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Ready?
They're so crispy.
Every box is delicious.
I could eat it forever.
I love boxes.
Delicious!
It tastes like chocolate love in this landscape.
I can't believe you're eating it.
Where are you eating?
It's the best time of my life. I could eat this for the rest of my life.
Next, takoyaki. Yes!
It's done!
It's done! It looks good!
It's absolutely delicious! It's absolutely delicious!
It's absolutely hot! Did you get it in one bite?
Yes! It's hot, isn't it! Mmm!
Open the mask!
Yummy!
Octopus!
Open!
The part that opens when you eat it.
The octopus is amazing!
So resilient!
You don't eat octopus this fresh.
I thought I was eating the octopus I'd just caught, but I'm really...
I'm so grateful.
Thank you very much.
This is the big octopus you just saw.
I'd like to try it.
Bon appétit.
It's chewy.
Gori-gori-gori-yummy.
Hagar, it's so hard it won't stick.
But yes, so today I caught Papa, boiled him, and cooked him into takoyaki.
I've never eaten takoyaki before in my life.
I've never eaten takoyaki like this before in my life, so it was a great experience.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
If we lose the Ashiben, you'll all have a nice fishing holiday, won't you?
So, I'd like you all to take a look at this... and see if anyone can catch more than four fish in two hours.
Good luck, good luck, good luck!